supermeatboy.com 2019-12-28

# Team Meat - Privacy Policy - Super Meat Boy Forever

Super Meat Boy Forever is brought to you by Team Meat. The following Privacy Policy applies to Super Meat Boy Forever (the "Game"), any related web sites and your unique player account, if any. 

When choosing to participate and opening a player account on the console platform or portal where you acquired the Game you may be granting access to certain information such as your name, email address, and other information you have shared with everyone in various activities in the Game and using our services and applications. You may also provide certain personally identifiable information, some of which is required for you to be able to acquire the Game or that may be used to enhance your player experience. All of this information obtained from you will be collectively referred to as “Your Information.” Team Meat WILL NOT share Your Information with anyone or any organization; Your Information WILL NEVER be sold or distributed in any form, or for any purpose unless approved by you, the account holder. 

Team Meat may also offer you the opportunity to "opt in" to receive additional email communications including Team Meat News Releases related to all the latest breaking news, the launch of new Team Meat games and announcements of all new Super Meat Boy Forever options and features. Team Meat may use Your Information for a minimum level of communication needed for a Player to play effectively and to enhance your experience in the Game or related web sites. 

Any of Your Information received by Team Meat will be maintained on a secure server and only qualified staff have access to that information. Super Meat Boy Forever may track how and when customers play the Game. We may also use cookies to track traffic on related web sites. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web surfing easier by saving your passwords and other preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you’ll find most major web sites use them. Cookies also help us to see which areas of the site are popular and which are not. We can then improve the site based on this information. 

If at any time a you indicate that you no longer want to receive communications from Team Meat, or if you wish to cancel your account, change or correct any of Your Information, you are free to do so and Your Information will be deleted, changed or corrected as requested. 

Team Meat would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following: 

The right to access - You have the right to request Team Meat for copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service. 

The right to rectification - You have the right to request that Team Meat correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request Team Meat to complete information you believe is incomplete. 

The right to erasure - You have the right to request that Team Meat erase your personal data, under certain conditions. 

The right to restrict processing - You have the right to request that Team Meat restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions. 

The right to object to processing - You have the right to object to Team Meat's processing of your personal data, under certain conditions. 

The right to data portability - You have the right to request that Team Meat transfer the data that we have received or collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions. 

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us. 

Email: support@supermeatboy.com 

Call us at: (401) 859-1847 

Or write to us:   
Team Meat   
PO Box 3464   
Kirkland, WA 98083 

The Game and the related websites may contain links to other sites; we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

A Special Note About Children Under 13 Years of Age. 

The Game and websites related to the Game are not intended for persons under the age of 13. They were not developed for or directed at children in any way. We do not knowingly solicit or collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly market or offer our Game or websites to children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years of age do not provide any personal information to us. If you are a parent or guardian and learn that your child have provided us with any such information, please let us know and we will immediately remove that information from our database. 

Team Meat will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. Super Meat Boy Forever will obtain your opt-in consent for any updates to this Privacy Policy that materially expand any sharing or use of Your Information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Policy at the time you register. 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, feel free to contact us at support@supermeatboy.com.
